bigtitscurvyasses.com 2011-06-10

# Privacy Statement

**PRIVACY POLICY for Servorama LTD  
**

**Effective as of July 1, 2010 (the "Effective Date")**

Your privacy is very important to us.  We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy.  This Privacy Policy (the "Policy") explains what information we collect about you and what we do with it.  We want you to fully understand our privacy practices and therefore, in addition to this Policy, we have created a Privacy Contact whom you can contact with any questions or concerns (see below).  We reserve the right to modify this Policy at any time, and we will notify you of any material changes to the Policy by posting the modified Policy on this page and changing the Effective Date at the top. We encourage you to check this page periodically for any changes.  This Policy is incorporated into, and subject to, the terms of our Terms and Conditions of Subscription.  By using or navigating our site you acknowledge that you have read, understand and agree to be bound by this Policy or any modified Policy as posted. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not use or visit the Web Site.

**What information do we collect?**   
We do not collect personally identifiable information except where you specifically provide us with such information.  We may collect your full name, e-mail address, street address and telephone number. We may also collect credit card information from you. We generally collect this personal information on our registration and order forms when you sign up to receive products or services from our Web Site and to access our member's area.    
We collect aggregate technical information (such as IP addresses, screen resolution, browser language, etc.) and anonymous demographic information (such as your postal or zip code, the web site that you came from, etc.) during your usage of the Web Site.

**What do we do with the information we collect?**  
We use personal information and other demographic or profile information you provide to us to: fulfill your orders or requests; attempt to prevent fraudulent transactions; verify your age, and; contact you when necessary.  Your personal information is NEVER shared with advertisers and market researchers.  
Whenever possible, we use non-identifiable information (i.e. IP addresses and anonymous demographic information) rather than personal information.  Non-identifiable information is used to tailor your experiences on our Web Site by showing content in which we think you will be interested and displaying content according to your preferences. We may use aggregate data to analyze user behaviour and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of our Web Site.  We also use the information collected to evaluate and improve our services and analyze traffic to our Web Site.  
Personal information collected on our Web Site is stored and processed in the United States and by using our Web Site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.  It is important for you to note that the laws on holding data in the United States may be less stringent than the laws of your country, but we intend to adhere to the principles set forth in this Policy.

**Do we share the information we collect with third parties?**  
We NEVER sell, provide or otherwise transfer your personally identifiable information to any arm-length third parties for any reason.  We are opposed to spam mail activities and does not participate in such mailings, nor do we release or authorize the use of membership data for such purposes.  We may transfer information between our affiliates.  We may transfer your information to a third party as a result of a sale, acquisition, merger or reorganization involving the Web Site, its affiliates or related companies and/or any of their respective assets.  
We may use statistical analysis of aggregate information to inform advertisers of aggregate user demographics and behaviour, as well as the number of users that have been exposed to or clicked on their advertising banners.  We will provide only aggregate data from these analyses to third parties. We may share information we collect with third party service providers to manage certain aspects of the services we provide, such as maintaining our servers and processing or fulfilling orders for products and services you purchase through the Web Site.  We ensure that the third party service providers that we share your information with have privacy policies in place substantially similar to our own.  
We may also disclose your information in special cases if required to do so by law, court order or other governmental authority or when we believe in good faith that disclosing this information is otherwise necessary or advisable, including, for instance, to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interfering with the rights or property of the Web Site, another user or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities (ie. for identify theft or fraud). 

**How long do we retain information?**  
We retain personal information for such period of time as we feel is necessary to ensure that you have a reasonable opportunity to access the information.  If you no longer consent to us retaining your personal information, you can contact us and request that it be removed at our support page.

**Do we save any correspondence that you send to us?**  
Yes. If you send us correspondence, including e-mails and faxes, we may retain such information in the records of your account.  We may also retain customer service correspondence and other correspondence from us to you.  We may retain these records in order to measure and improve our customer service, and investigate potential fraud and violation of our Terms and Conditions of Subscription.  We may, over time, delete these records if permitted by law.

**Is the information submitted in public forums confidential?**  
No. The Web Site may offer chat rooms, forums, message boards and/or news groups to our users. IT IS IMPORTANT TO REMEMBER THAT ANY INFORMATION DISCLOSED IN THESE AREAS BECOMES PUBLIC INFORMATION.  Accordingly, you should exercise extreme caution when deciding to disclose your personal information and you do so at your own risk.

**Do we use cookies?**  
Yes. Cookies are pieces of information (actually, alphanumeric identifiers) generated by web servers and stored in your computer for future access.  Cookies cannot view or retrieve data from other cookies, nor can they capture files or data stored on your computer.  We use cookie technology to enhance your online experience by making it easier for you to navigate through our Web Site or make a feature work better.  We also use cookies to track affiliates that refer you to our Web Site.  These particular cookies are saved on your computer for 30 days and collect no data from you.  Generally, cookies can be disabled.  The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether.  If you would like to use the Web Site, you may do so without accepting cookies.  However, you should understand that if you choose not to accept cookies, some areas of the Web Site may not function properly or optimally and you will not be permitted to access certain secured areas of the Web Site. 

**Do we use web beacons?**  
Yes. The Web Site may contain electronic images known as "web beacons" or single-pixel gifs that allow us to count visitors to our Web Site and collect aggregate data. Web beacons collect limited information including cookie number, time and date of a page view and a description of the page on which the web beacon resides.

**Is the Web Site secure?**  
We are committed to maintaining the security of your information and have measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.  We employ the latest and most secure techniques available for protecting our systems from intrusion by unauthorized individuals, and we are constantly upgrading our security as better methods become available. Our data center utilizes state-of-the-art physical security measures to prevent unauthorized access to the facility.  In addition, all information is stored in a secure location behind a firewall and other sophisticated security systems with limited (need-to-know) administrative access.  It is "IP protected" and only accessible by authorized employees using a certified IP address.  All employees who have access to, or are associated with, the processing of personal information are contractually obligated to respect the confidentiality of your information and abide by the privacy standards we have established.  Although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.

**Does this Policy apply to linked web sites other than the Web Site?**  
No. The Web Site contains links to other Internet web sites.  By clicking on a third party advertising banner or other link, you will be redirected off the Web Site and to such third party web site.  Furthermore, we may permit third parties to offer subscription and/or registration-based services through our Web Site.  We are not responsible for the privacy policies of such web sites. You should make sure that you read and understand the privacy policies of the third party web sites and direct any concerns regarding external links to the third party web site administrator or webmaster prior to providing any personally identifiable information.

**How do you unsubscribe?**  
We sometimes email you in order to provide targeted marketing from our Web Site and related services.  All emails you receive from us will include specific instructions on how to unsubscribe and you may unsubscribe at any time. Additionally, we give you the following options for removing your information from our database:  
(1) contact us at our support site. (2) select the opt-out link at the bottom of any email and follow the instructions provided;   

**Can we update/correct your information?**  
Yes.  You may correct or update your personal information by writing to our Support site.
